Johnny Otis Collection, 1949-2012 SC 106
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 6. Photographs
  - Three unidentified saxophonists, unidentified man at microphone, unidentified man (Big Joe Turner?) and two unidentified guitarists (Shuggie Otis?) performing at Shelly's Manne-Hole, 1960-1972; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000237
  - Johnny Otis playing vibraphone and two unidentified saxophonists performing at Shelly's Manne-Hole, 1960-1972; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005738
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000238
  - Unidentified guitarist, unidentified man at microphone, unidentified man (Big Joe Turner?), unidentified guitarist (Shuggie Otis?), and three unidentified saxophonists performing at Shelly's Manne-Hole, 1960-1972; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005739
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000239
  - Unidentified guitarist (Shuggie Otis?), three unidentified saxophonists and Johnny Otis on vibraphone performing at Shelly's Manne-Hole, 1960-1972; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005740
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000240
  - Unidentified guitarists, unidentified saxophone, unidentified man at microphone, unidentified singer (Big Joe Turner?), two unidentified saxophones and unidentified guitarist (Shuggie Otis?) performing at Shelly's Manne-Hole, 1960-1972; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005741
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000241
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis and unidentified male and female bandmates, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005742
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000242
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis and unidentified male and female bandmates, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005743
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000243
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis and unidentified male and female bandmates, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005744
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000244
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at piano and unidentified bandmates and female trumpet player, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005745
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000245
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at piano and unidentified bandmates and female trumpet player, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005746
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000246
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at piano and unidentified bandmates and female trumpet player, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005747
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000247
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at piano and unidentified bandmates and female trumpet player, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005748
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000248
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at piano and unidentified bandmates and female trumpet player, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005749
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000249
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis seated and unidentified man in sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005750
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000250
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis seated and unidentified man in sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005751
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000251
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis seated and unidentified man in sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005752
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000252
  - Publicity shot of unidentified man in sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005753
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000253
  - Publicity shot of unidentified man in sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005754
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000254
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with mallets, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005755
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000255
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with mallets, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005756
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000256
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with mallets, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005757
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000257
  - Publicity shot of unidentified female trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005758
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000258
  - Publicity shot of unidentified female trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005759
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000259
  - Publicity shot of unidentified female trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005760
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000260
  - Publicity shot of unidentified female trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005761
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000261
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with mallets and unidentified trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005762
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000262
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with arm around unidentified female trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005763
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000263
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with mallets and unidentified trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005764
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000264
  - Publicity shot of Johnny Otis at vibraphone with mallets and unidentified trumpet player with sunglasses, 1976; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005765
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000265
  - Unidentified child [Shuggie Otis?], 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005766
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000266
  - Johnny Otis, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005767
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000267
  - Johnny Otis (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005768
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000268
  - Johnny Otis (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005769
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000269
  - Johnny Otis in captain's hat with dog, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005770
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000270
  - Unidentified child [Shuggie Otis?] with dog, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005771
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000271
  - Unidentified man in hat, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005772
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000272
  - Four unidentified men (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005773
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000273
  - Unidentified man in glasses (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005774
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000274
  - Johnny Otis and unidentified children, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005775
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000275
  - Johnny Otis, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005776
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000276
  - [Obscured], 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005777
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000277
  - Unidentified girl with camera and unidentified boy [Shuggie Otis?], 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005778
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000278
  - [Obscured], 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005779
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000279
  - Johnny Otis with camera, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005780
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000280
  - Johnny Otis with camera, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005781
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000281
  - Johnny Otis with camera, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005782
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000282
  - Unidentified child [Shuggie Otis?] and unidentified barber (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005783
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000283
  - Unidentified child [Shuggie Otis?] in elephant shaped barber chair and unidentified barber, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005784
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000284
  - Unidentified child [Shuggie Otis?] and unidentified barber, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005785
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000285
  - Unidentified woman with glasses (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005786
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000286
  - Birds in coop, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005787
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000287
  - [Obscured], 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005788
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000288
  - Unidentified child [Shuggie Otis?] sleeping, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005789
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000289
  - Unidentified man in hat, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005790
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000290
  - Three unidentified men (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005791
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000291
  - Blurry (obsured) photo of picture on wall, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005792
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000292
  - Unidentified man in diner, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005793
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000293
  - Three unidentified individuals (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005794
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000294
  - Unidentified man, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005795
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000295
  - Five unidentified men in recording studio with instruments, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005796
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000296
  - Five unidentified men in recording studio with instruments, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005797
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000297
  - Four unidentified men in recording studio with instruments, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005798
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000298
  - Five unidentified men in recording studio with instruments, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005799
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000299
  - Five unidentified men in recording studio with instruments, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005800
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000300
  - Four unidentified people in office, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005801
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000301
  - [Obscured], 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005802
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000302
  - Unidentified man pretending to strangle unidentified woman standing next to an animal house, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005803
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000303
  - Unidentified man and woman standing next to an animal house, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005804
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000304
  - Unidentified woman and child sitting in a Ford Sunliner with an unidentified man and three unidentified children standing next to the car, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005805
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000305
  - Unidentified woman seated outdoors, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005806
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000306
  - Unidentified woman and child outdoors, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005807
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000307
  - Unidentified child outdoors, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005808
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000308
  - Two unidentified girls outdoors, 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005809
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000309
  - Three unidentified children playing outdoors (obscured), 1960-1969; 1 negative b&w; 8 x 11 mm.
    PA005810
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000310
  - Johnny Otis with Sam Cooke, 1 Photograph black and white; 8 x 10 in.
    PA000183
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000311
  - Flyer for show with King Cole Trio, Johnnie Otis, and Eddie Green, 1 Photograph black and white; 7 x 10 in.
    PA000184
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000312
  - Johnny Otis publicity portrait, 1 Photograph black and white; 8 x 10 in.
    PA000185
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000313
  - Johnny Otis and Sally Blair, 1 Photograph black and white; 8 x 10 in.
    PA000186
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000314
  - Johnny Otis & The Fox, 1 Photograph black and white; 8 x 10 in.
    PA000187
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000315
  - Johnny Otis sitting with unidentified person, 1 Photograph black and white; 8 x 10 in.
    PA000188
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000316
  - Johnny Otis on stage with unidentified performers at Nite Life Club, 1956; 1 Photograph black and white; 8 x 10 in.
    PA000189
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000317